我出生在宇宙中
I was born in space.
我從未感受過陽光照在我臉上
I've never felt the sun on my face,
從未呼吸過真正的空氣
or breathed real air,
從未在水中漂浮過
or floated in the water,
我們都從未試過
none of us have.
整整三代以來
For 3 generations,
方舟維持了剩下的人類的生存
the Ark has kept what's left of the human race alive.
但如今  我們的家園瀕臨毀滅
But now our home is dying,
而我們  是人類最后的希望
and we, are the last hope of mankind.
100個人被派往地球
100 prisoners sent on a
執行一項孤注一擲的任務
desperate mission to the ground.
來這的每個人都是因為違反過法律
Each of us is here because we broke the law.
而地球上  沒有法律
On the ground, there is no law.
我們要做的只有生存
All we have to do is survive.
但我們將接受考驗
But we will be tested,
接受地球的考驗
by the earth,
接受這里所隱藏的秘密的考驗
by the secrets it hides,
最重要的是  接受相互的考驗
and most of all, by each other.
《地球百子》前情提要
Previously on "The 100"...
-鎮定  -對他們來說我們
- Calm down! - We're dead
已經死了  沒人在乎
to them! And we're alone!
有人在乎
You're not alone!
我在乎你
You're not alone.
雷文
Raven!
芬
Finn!
議會在表決是否要處決300人
The council is voting whether to kill 300 people
以節省氧氣
to save air.
我們得告訴他們
We have to tell them!
無線電丟了
The radio's gone.
媽求你了  讓我去找個醫生吧
Mom, please, let me get a doctor.
不行  你不能告訴任何人
No! You can't tell anyone.
告訴我如果有人知道了會怎樣  說
Tell me what happens if you do. Say it.
你會被流放
Y-you get floated.
我不懂
I don't understand.
要第二個孩子有什么錯
Why is it wrong to have more than one baby?
方舟不可能永遠維持
The Ark couldn't survive.
所以法官不能允許
The chancellor can't allow it.
他就像奧古斯都大帝
He's, like, the emperor Augustus, right?
沒錯
That's right.
就像書里寫的那個皇帝
Just like the emperor we read about.
孩子要出來了  拿毯子來
The baby's coming. Get the blanket.
勇敢的孩子
My brave boy.
你有個妹妹了
You have a sister.
給她起個名字吧
You should name her.
奧古斯都大帝也有個妹妹
Augustus had a sister.
奧克塔維亞
Octavia.
貝拉米  讓她別哭了
Bellamy, you can't let her cry.
把她給我
Here. Give her to me.
不  媽  你不能睡
No, mom, mom, you can't fall asleep.
我太累了
I'm so tired.
你妹妹
Your sister.
就交給你了
Your responsibility.
媽  我該怎么做  媽
Mom, mom, what do I do? Mom!
別出聲  拜托了
Shh. Please.
看  我說過了吧  沒事了
See? I told you. It's ok.
我不會讓你受到傷害的  奧克塔維亞
I won't let anything bad happen to you, Octavia.
我保證
I promise.
奧克塔維亞
Octavia!
你醒著嗎
You're up?
想著方舟上幾百個人
Yeah. Knowing that hundreds of people
可能就要死亡
might be dying on the Ark
讓人難以入睡
makes it pretty hard to sleep.
雷文的燃燒棒會成功的
Raven's flares will work.
無線電的成功幾率肯定更大
Her radio would've worked better.
你見到奧克塔維亞了嗎
Have you seen Octavia?
沒  不過那是奧克塔維亞啊
No. It's octavia.
她可能出去追蝴蝶什么的了
She's probably chasing butterflies.
克拉克  我找了整個營地
Clarke, I've checked the camp.
她不在
She's not here.
好吧  我會幫你找到她
Ok. I'll help you find her.
再找一遍吧
Let's check again.
你去看運輸船
You go to the dropship.
我去營地里其他地方找找
I'll check the rest of the tents.
謝謝你
Thank you.
別謝我  我這么做不是為了你
Don't thank me. I'm not doing this for you.
是為了奧克塔維亞
I'm doing it for Octavia.
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
翻譯 木淺薰  Reginamoon  DustD  莉莉絲
翻譯  乖寶寶運氣好  瀟湘月影  薩薩
時間軸 三水  萌   后期 寶寶
校對 薩薩  總監 薩薩
求求你  求求你別傷害我
Please, please don't hurt me.
求求你別  不要
Please don't--No!
不要  不要  求你了  不要
No! No, please! No! No!
地球百子
第一季  第六集
大伙兒  都過來拿把武器
Hey, everybody, gather around and grab a weapon.
我妹妹獨自在外已經12個小時了
My sister's been out there alone for 12 hours.
都武裝起來  找不到她絕不回來
Arm up. We're not coming back without her.
賈斯珀  你沒必要這么做的
Hey, Jasper, you don't have to do this.
我們把你帶回來之后你還沒出過營地呢
You haven't left camp since we brought you back.
克拉克  我必須這么做
Clarke, I need to do this.
我們需要用上所有的人手
We need all the people we can get.
我們需要一個追蹤者
We need a tracker.
芬  快出來
Finn. Get out here.
你想少一只耳朵嗎
You want to lose an ear?
真不能相信你在監獄里留了這么長的頭發
Can't believe you let it get so long in lockup.
不能等到早上再剪嗎
This couldn't wait till morning?
我突然來了靈感  所以...
I was inspired. So...
你想和我聊什么
what did you want to talk about?
沒什么
Nothing.
那個不急
It can wait.
你臉上的表情可不是"沒什么"的意思
That wasn't your "nothing" face.
這是"我要去太空漫步"的意思
That was your "going on a spacewalk" face.
我保證不會再去太空漫步了
No more spacewalks.
去休息吧  好嗎
Get some rest, ok?
芬  我們得走了
Finn, we're leaving.
好的  我就來
All right. I'm coming.
等等
Hey, wait.
發型不錯
Nice hair.
我們得談談
We should talk about this.
你有女朋友了  芬
You have a girlfriend, Finn.
真的沒什么可說的了
There's really nothing left to say.
別走
Hey, hold on.
是真的
It's true.
我在意雷文
I care about Raven.
但是你和我  我們擦出過火花
But you and me, we started something.
不是什么不能終止的事情
It's nothing we can't stop.
你確定嗎
Are you sure?
因為我可不確定
Because I'm not.
大伙兒們  快過來
Guys, guys. Come here!
看見那個了嗎
Did you see that?
看那上面
Look up there.
太美了
It's so beautiful.
燃燒棒沒起作用
They didn't work.
他們沒看見那些燃燒棒
They didn't see the flares.
難道從一場流星雨你就看出來了
A meteor shower tells you that?
那不是流星雨  那是葬禮
It's not a meteor shower, it's a funeral.
幾百具尸體從方舟上被送回了地球
Hundreds of bodies being returned to the earth from the ark.
從地球上看來就像是流星雨一般
This is what it looks like from the other side.
他們沒收到我們的信息
They didn't get our message.
這都怪你
This is all because of you!
我幫你找到了無線電
I helped you find the radio.
在你把它從我艙里偷走且毀了它之后
Yeah, after you jacked it from my pod and trashed it!
沒錯  他清楚這一點
Yeah, he knows.
而且從現在開始他得背負這后果
Now has to live with it.
我只知道我妹妹還在外面
All I know is that my sister is out there
而我必須找到她
and I'm gonna find her.
你們來還是不來
You coming or what?
是啊
Yeah.
那我們還等什么
What are we waiting for?
出發吧
Move out!
我們得和他們取得聯系
We have to talk to them.
300人不夠的
300 won't be enough.
氧氣量會不斷下降
The oxygen level will just keep dropping.
假如我們不告訴他們
And if we don't tell them that
在地球上是可以生存的
they can survive down here,
他們會殺掉更多人
They'll kill more people.
-他們別無選擇  -伙計們
- They have to. - Guys...
他們要走了  咱們得動身了
They're leaving. We gotta go.
我必須得去
I gotta do this.
你應該留下來修好無線電  好嗎
And you should stay and fix the radio, ok?
怎么修  發送器都砸碎了
Fix it? The transmitter's smashed.
除非有零件空降下來
Unless there's a parts depot down here,
不然我們無法和方舟對話
we're not talking to the ark.
藝術品補給店
Art supply store.
我知道有個地方也許能給你弄到發送器
I know a place you might be able to get a transmitter.
太好了
Great.
看起來你要和我一起來了
It looks like you're coming with me instead.
芬  沒有你我們找不到她
Finn? We're not gonna find her without you.
小心點
Be careful.
我愛你
I love you.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
這邊走
It's this way.
你好
Hello?
有人在嗎
Is anybody here?
他給縫好了
He fixed it?
看啊  過來
Look! Over here!
那是什么
What is it?
就在那  你看到了嗎
Right there. You see it?
那是奧克塔維亞的吧
Is that Octavia's?
繩子
Rope.
你干什么
What are you doing?
咱們需要繩子爬上來
We need the rope to get back up.
手電筒
Flashlight.
是她的
It's hers.
我要下到底下去
I'm going all the way down.
有別人在這里
Someone else was here.
往那邊的印記更深一點
The prints are deeper going that way.
他帶走了她
He was carrying her.
如果他們帶走了她  那她還活著
If they took her, she's alive.
和他們帶走我的時候一樣
Like when they took me.
我不懂地球語
I don't speak grounder...
但我可以肯定這意味著禁止入內
but I'm pretty sure this means keep out.
-咱們走吧  -簡直瘋了
- Let's get out of here. - It's crazy.
我走了
I'm outta here.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
想回去就回去吧
Go back if you want.
我的妹妹  我的責任
My sister, my responsibility.
即便是下地獄  我也要找到她
I'd walk into hell to find her.
我覺得咱們已經下了
I think we just did.
走啦
Go!
我還要再騎一次小馬
I want another pony ride.
你還要騎啊
You want another one?
好吧  你想穿過叢林野地還是森林
Ok, you want to go through the jungle or the forest?
我想看方舟  貝爾
I want to see the ark, Bell.
把我帶出門去
Take me out the door.
夠了  你們倆
That's enough. Both of you.
到時間了
It's time.
可是  不要
But--no.
我不想回去
I don't want to!
你怎么可能知道
How do you even know?
是啊媽媽  告訴我們
Yeah, mom, tell us
你為什么不會被突擊檢查突擊到
why you're never surprised by surprise inspections.
管好你自己  貝拉米·布萊克
Mind yourself, Bellamy Blake.
告訴你妹妹如果被他們找到會發生什么
Tell your sister what happens if they find her.
她知道會發生什么
She knows what happens.
你告訴過她幾千遍了
You've told her a thousand times.
你知道該怎么辦
Oh. You know the drill.
我恨這事
I hate the drill.
有時候我真希望自己沒被生出來
Sometimes I wish I was never even born.
住口  奧克塔維亞  我知道你害怕
Stop it, Octavia. I know you're afraid,
而恐懼是個魔鬼
but fear is a demon.
閉上眼睛  然后告訴你自己
Close your eyes and tell yourself
你一點都不害怕
that you are not afraid.
這樣就能把惡魔殺掉
That is how you slay the demon.
開門  臨檢
Dectation! Open up!
講一遍
Say it.
我不害怕
I'm not afraid.
乖
Ok.
立刻開門
Open the door, now!
布萊克女士  我們受議會之命
Miss Blake, by authority of the council,
來這進行一次隨機檢查
we're here to perform a random inspection.
格魯斯檢察官  很高興見到你
Inspector Grus, it's good to see you.
你的制服已經補好了
Your uniform's ready.
給  跟新的一樣
There you go. Just like new.
你有什么東西要給我嗎
Do you have something for me?
貝拉米的推薦信
Bellamy's letter of recommendation.
小子  你認為你是當警衛的料嗎
You think you're guard material, kid?
到這來  讓我好好看看你
Come here. Let's have a look at you.
不用了  謝謝
I'm good, thanks.
貝拉米
Bellamy.
-站起來  快點  -我不害怕
- Stand up. Now. - I'm not afraid.
我不害怕
I'm not afraid.
我不想過去
I don't think so.
你到底想不想當警衛
You want to be in the guard or not?
我數三個數  趕緊過來
Come here. 3 seconds.
一  二
1...2...
貝拉米  對不起  檢察官
Bellamy! I'm so sorry, inspector.
-我  -不用道歉
- I-- -Don't be.
也許當警衛能使他成長為一個男人
Maybe the guard will make a man out of him.
-把它收拾干凈  -是  長官
- Clean that up. - Sir.
長官  這個房間沒問題
Yes sir, this one got clear.
一會兒到我的住處來
Come to my quarters later.
我就給你他的推薦信
He'll get that recommendation.
我不害怕  我不害怕
I'm not afraid. I'm not afraid.
我不害怕
I'm not afraid.
它們真漂亮
They're so beautiful.
雷文  我知道你昨天才到這
Raven, I know you just got here yesterday,
但我們可沒時間賞花
but we don't have time for this.
快來
Come on.
抓緊時間拯救世界
Hurry up and save the world.
你和你媽媽真像
You're just like your mom.
我和她一點兒都不像
I'm nothing like my mom.
別緊張  我是夸獎你啊
Relax. That's a compliment.
艾比可厲害了呢
Abby's a badass.
那個吊艙就是她的主意
The pod was her idea.
不能和我一起下來
It broke her heart
她肯定特別傷心
not being able to come down with me,
但她一直都相信你還活著
but she never stopped believing you were alive.
是啊  她真是年度好媽媽
Yeah. Mother of the year.
我媽媽幾乎從來沒有陪伴過我
Well, my mom was awol most of my life.
等她一無所有的時候才會出現
When she did show up, it was empty-handed.
她會生下我肯定是為了
Pretty sure she had me just to trade in
拿我的配給去換酒喝
my rations for moonshine.
那你靠什么生存
How'd you survive?
鄰居家的男孩  芬
Boy next door. Finn.
他把他那份配給分給我  記得我的生日
He shared his rations. Remembered my birthday.
救我的命
Saved my life.
他就是我的家人
He's my family.
什么都沒找到
I got nothing.
找不到蹤跡了
We lost the trail.
繼續找
Keep looking.
這樣漫無目的地找不是辦法
Wandering around aimlessly isn't the way to find your sister.
我們應該原路返回
We should backtrack...
我不回去
I'm not going back.
約翰哪去了
Hey, where's John?
他剛才還在這
I just saw him a second ago.
分開找  他不可能走遠
Spread out. He couldn't have gotten that far.
他們藏在樹上
They use the trees.
我們不應該越界
We shouldn't have crossed the boundary.
我們能回去了嗎
Now can we go back?
在那
There.
一個
One.
還有一個
Another one.
我們應該快跑
We should run.
我們試試這個
Let's try this one.
你怎么找到這個地方的
How did you find this place?
不是我找到的  是芬找到的
I didn't. Finn found it.
這能行嗎
Hey, will this work?
太好了
Sweet.
RF  無線電頻率
Rf. Radio frequency.
如果我們能找到控制器
If we can just find the controller,
就太棒了
we'll be golden.
好吧
All right.
芬做的嗎
Finn made this.
是的
Oh, uh, yeah.
我們看到只雙頭鹿
we saw this two-headed deer
就在第一天到地球上的時候
our first day on the ground.
歡迎來到天堂  對吧
Welcome to paradise, right?
找到了
Got it.
芬總是這樣
Finn always does that.
在意外中發現美好
Finds the beauty in the unexpected.
可以走了嗎
Good to go?
趕緊去拯救世界  對吧
Hurry up and save the world, right?
是啊  我們可以走了
Yeah. We're good. Ok.
快走  我們走
S go! Let's go!
我們該怎么辦  他們一直追著我們
What are we gonna do? They keep heading us off.
不停地跑
Second man: Just keep running.
我跑不動了
I can't run much longer!
我不會為了他停下來的
I'm not stopping for him!
我受夠了逃跑了
I'm sick of running anyway.
你在干嗎
Hey, what are you doing?
他們知道她在哪里
They know where she is.
迪格斯  你在哪里
Diggs, where are you?
羅瑪
Roma!
等一下  羅瑪  可能還有  快停下
Wait! Roma. Could be more. Stop.
他們把我們引到這里的
They were leading us here.
我們只能跑進這里來
It's the only direction we could run in.
他們會去哪
Hey. Where'd they go?
去追羅瑪
After Roma.
你絕對猜不到接下來有什么好事
You'll never guess what's about to happen.
檢查唄  我要進洞了
Inspection. I'll get in the hole.
不不不  坐下  坐好
No, no, no, no, no. Sit, sit.
這太棒了
This is great.
拜托  貝爾  我不想再聽
Please, Bell, I don't want to hear
什么美妙的月出了
about another amazing moonrise
我永遠都不能看見
When I'm never gonna be able to see one.
你現在就能看到
You're going to see one right now.
團結日化裝舞會
The unity day masquerade dance
10分鐘后開始
starts in 10 minutes.
現在  本來我什么都不想說
Now, I didn't want to say anything
直到我確定我的實習組
until I was sure my cadet unit
負責安保工作
was working security.
我會在那里看著你
I'm gonna be there watching you
由始至終
the entire time.
你現在還不是守衛呢  實習生
You're not a guardsman yet, cadet.
真的嗎
This is real?
我看起來怎么樣
How do I look?
神秘莫測
Mysterious.
貝爾  媽媽怎么辦
Oh, Bell, what about mom?
你能別擔心了嗎
Hey, will you stop worrying?
沒等她發現你出去  我們就已經回來了
We'll be back before she even knows you're gone.
要出去走走嗎
Want to go for a walk?
沒事的
It's ok.
那是誰
Who's that?
另一個不會注意到我們的女孩
Another girl who won't notice us.
我的腿
My leg.
我要休息一下
I need to rest.
謝謝  你救了我
Thank you. You saved my life.
剛才那個女孩  我認識
That girl back there, I knew her,
如果她在這里  那我哥哥一定也在
So, if she's here, then so is my brother.
拜托你也幫幫他  他們會殺了他的
Please, you have to help him, too. They'll kill him.
你聽不懂我說話  對嗎  好極了
You don't understand me, do you? Great.
你為什么要照顧我
Why are you taking care of me?
你在山澗底下發現的我
You found me at the bottom of that ravine.
治好我的膝蓋
Fixed my knee.
你在干嘛
What the hell are you doing?
不要這樣
Please don't do this.
住手  住手
Aah! Stop it! No, stop it!
停下  拜托  請不要這樣
Stop! Please! Please don't do this.
她在這  羅瑪
There she is. Roma!
他們耍我們呢
They're playing with us.
她是因為我才來的
She only came because of me.
只要他們愿意  隨時可以殺死我們
They can kill us whenever they want.
那就趕緊的來個干脆的
Then they should get it over with!
來吧
Come on!
我們知道你們在那
We know you're out there!
你們想殺我們
You want to kill us...
貝拉米
Bellamy!
他們走了
They're leaving.
那個霧角  是什么意思
That horn. What does it mean?
酸霧
Acid fog.
我們得快跑
We have to run.
沒時間了
There's no time.
你的眼睛很漂亮
Nice eyes.
你是哪個站的
What station are you from?
太陽耀斑預警
Solar flare alert.
一個X級太陽耀斑已經開始了
An x-class solar flare has begun
在方舟的右舷
on the starboard side of the ark.
所有公民必須立刻至最近的避難區報到
All citizens must report to the nearest shelter zone immediately.
這不是演習  這是太陽耀斑預警
This is not a test. This is a solar flare alert.
貝爾  我得回家
Bell, I need to get home!
你會回去的
You will.
女士們先生們  你們知道該怎么做的
Ladies and gentlemen, you know the drill.
摘掉面具  出示身份證
Masks off. I.D. Chips out.
貝爾  我們該怎么辦
Bell, what do we do?
聽著  無論發生什么
Listen to me. Whatever happens,
你都得跑回家藏到地板下面
You get back home and get under the floor.
在那里  你會一如既往地安全的
You'll be safe there from the flare, like always.
你怎么辦
What are you gonna do?
我來掩護你  快
Create a distraction. Go on.
貝爾  我該怎么回家
Bell, how do I get home?
實習生布萊克  為何亮出武器
Cadet Blake. Why is your weapon out?
摘掉面具
Mask off.
長官  她沒事  我已經檢查過她了
Sir, she's--she's fine. I already scanned her.
你都沒有掃描器
You don't have a scanner.
請出示身份證
I.D., please.
拜托  沙姆韋中尉
Please, lieutenant Shumway,
求你了  放她走
I'm begging you, she needs to leave.
作為您的守衛同事
As a fellow guardsman...
請讓我們離開
just let us walk out of here
你讓我做什么都行
And I'll do anything you want.
任何事
Anything.
現在  出示身份證
I.D. Now.
攔住她
Stop her.
我們要等多久
How long are we supposed to wait?
這管用嗎
Will this even work?
我們會知道的
We'll find out.
不會的
No, we won't.
沒有霧
There's no fog.
也許是假警報
Maybe it was a false alarm.
他們回來了
They're coming back.
我想他是一個人
I think he's alone.
我們現在能跑了嗎
Now can we run?
他看不到我們  我要跟著他
He doesn't see us. I'm going after him.
然后呢  殺了他
And what? Kill him?
不  抓住他
No. Catch him.
逼他說出奧克塔維亞在哪
Make him tell me where Octavia is,
然后殺了他
Then kill him.
我們怎么知道他不會把我們領向另一個陷阱
How do we know he's not leading us to another trap?
不知道
We don't.
怎么樣了
How's it coming?
你沒事吧
Are you ok?
從地堡回來的一路上你都沒怎么說話
You hardly said a word the whole way back from the bunker.
-雷文  -告訴我我錯了
- Raven... - Tell me I'm wrong.
告訴我芬沒給你做這個
Tell me Finn didn't make this for you.
告訴我在我冒生命危險下來這里時
Tell me you weren't screwing my boyfriend
你沒在搞我的男朋友
as I was risking my ass to come down here.
我做不到
I can't tell you that.
他也為我做了一個
He made one for me, too.
你可一點不特別
Just in case you thought you were special.
你覺得我想這樣嗎
Do you think I wanted this?
我甚至不知道你的存在
I didn't even know you existed.
他以為你已經死了  雷文
Look, as far as he knew, you were dead, Raven.
他以為你沒來得及逃走
Or you would have been soon enough.
還有我媽媽
My mom, too,
還有方舟上我們認識的所有人
and everyone we ever knew on the ark,
我們沒辦法阻止
And there was nothing we could do to stop it.
僅僅十天  他本可以多等幾天的
He could've waited more than 10 days.
你愛他嗎
Do you love him?
我壓根不怎么了解他
I hardly know him.
-貝拉米  -奧克塔維亞
- Bellamy? - Octavia.
去拿鑰匙
Get the key.
門羅  守好入口
Monroe, watch the entrance.
沒事的  你沒事
It's ok. You're ok.
見習生布萊克
Cadet Blake.
現在是門衛布萊克了  中尉
It's Janitor Blake now, lieutenant.
是指揮官  這一年發生了很多事
Commander. A lot's changed in the past year.
我能進來嗎
May I?
是你親自把我媽媽流放
You've got some nerve coming here
你還敢到這兒來
after pushing the button that floated my mother.
我也是聽命行事
I was following orders.
你找我到底有什么事
What the hell do you want from me?
你是名優秀的士兵  貝拉米  你知道嗎
You were a hell of a guardsman, Bellamy, you know that?
機靈  勤奮  足智多謀
Smart, hardworking, resourceful.
我還不是名士兵
I wasn't a guardsman.
我記得你是這么說的
That's what you said. I remember.
你也說了你會不惜一切代價保護你妹妹
You also said you'd do anything to protect your sister.
我也記得
I remember, too.
我希望這話還有效
I hope that's still true.
她還好嗎
Is she ok?
我下面要告訴你的是機密事項
What I'm about to tell you is classified.
亞哈法官批準了一項
Chancellor Jaha has approved
重返地球的任務
a mission to earth.
他要把青少年囚犯派往地球
He's sending the juvenile prisoners to the ground.
共計一百人  你妹妹也在其中
100 of them. Your sister included.
不  不能這么做  這不安全
N-no. You can't. It's not safe.
你必須阻止他們
You have to stop them.
我也想阻止
I wish I could.
我只能給你在運輸船上安排一個座位
What I can do is get you a seat on that dropship.
你說得對
You're right.
那些孩子很難生還
It's doubtful those kids will survive,
但如果有你在
but if you're there,
至少奧克塔維亞不會孤單
At least Octavia won't be alone.
我要做什么
What do I have to do?
殺了法官
Kill the Chancellor.
不如我現在就把你殺了
How about I kill you instead?
殺了我  你妹妹就得獨自一人
Kill me and your sister goes alone
前往輻射遍地的星球
to a radiation-soaked planet
而你會像你母親一樣被流放
And you get floated like your mother.
飛船二十分鐘后出發  貝拉米
Ship launches in 20 minutes, Bellamy.
如果你答應  我們得走了
If you're gonna do this, we have to leave.
馬上就走
Right now.
你是怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
我們跟蹤他找來的
Followed him.
我們走吧  在他醒來之前快走
We should go. Now. Before he wakes up.
我不會讓他醒過來了
He's not gonna wake up.
貝拉米  住手
Bellamy, stop.
他沒有傷害我  我們走吧
He didn't hurt me. Let's just go.
這戰爭是他們先挑起的  芬  讓開
They started this. Finn. Move.
霧角
Foghorn.
住手  那是我哥哥
Stop! That's my brother!
克拉克  克拉克在哪
Clarke! Where's clarke?
字幕
Get clarke now.
我在這  怎么了
Hey. I'm here. What's up?
奧克塔維亞
Octavia.
芬  芬
Finn. Finn?
我的天吶  天吶
Oh, my god. Oh, oh, my god.
天吶
Oh, my god.
他還活著
He's alive.
貝拉米不讓我把刀拔出來
Bellamy wouldn't let me take the knife out.
這是對的
No, that was a good call.
把他帶到運輸船去  快點
Get him in the dropship now. Go!
克拉克  你能救他嗎
Clarke, can you save him?
不  我不不行  得讓我媽媽幫忙
No. Not me. I need my mother.
我得和她溝通
I need to talk to her.
但無線電不能用啊
There's still no radio.
雷文  修好它  快點
Raven, fix it! Go!
你還好嗎
Hey, you ok?
我沒事  你快去吧
Ok. Yeah. Just go.
你剛才為什么護著他
Why were you defending him?
因為他救了我的命
Because he saved my life.
刺中羅瑪的長矛其實是用來...
That spear that hit Roma was actually meant...
不  你搞錯了  是我救了你的命
No, you're wrong. I saved your life.
你怎么知道  他把你救活
For all you know, he was keeping you alive
不是為了拿你當活誘
to use you as bait for one of their traps.
不  我不覺得他會這么做
No. I don't think so.
你不覺得...  這就是問題所在
You don't think, o! That's the problem.
他們今天殺了三個我們的同伴
They killed 3 of our people today.
如果你當時不阻止我
And if you would've let me kill him
讓我把他殺了
when I had the chance,
芬現在也不會生命垂危了
Finn wouldn't be in there dying right now.
別把你的錯都安到我頭上來
Stop blaming me for your mistakes.
芬的遭遇不是我的錯
What happened to Finn is not my fault.
我當時想盡快離開  如果芬死在那
I wanted to leave, so if Finn dies in there,
那也是你的錯
that's on you.
一切的不幸
Everything that's gone wrong
都是因為你
is because of you.
你害我被鎖在方舟上
You got me locked up on the ark.
是你讓我去那該死的舞會
You wanted me to go to that stupid dance.
是你害媽媽被殺了
You got mom killed!
是我
Me?
媽媽會被流放是因為生了你
Mom was floated for having you.
她會死是因為你活著
She's dead because you're alive.
那是她的選擇
That was her choice.
我無從選擇
I didn't have a choice.
從你出生那天我的人生就結束了
My life ended the day you were born.
你去哪
Where do you think you're going?
你不能永遠把我鎖在這
You can't keep me locked up in here forever.
回營地去
Get inside.
馬上
Go!
風暴將至
A storm's coming.